<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fonts on Type Services</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fonts on Type Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:30:19 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/fonts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Risqué</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/risque/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:30:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/risque/</guid>
      <description>Hand painted using oil pastel, each glyph is full of character and unique texture creating a natural, hand drawn feel. Perfect for display use in a wide range of creative projects and graphic applications including posters, digital painting, illustration and more.&#xA;Download it free Includes: EOT, OTF, TTF, WOFF &amp;amp; WOFF2 formats. One font weight Upper, Lowercase Western European Language Support Punctuation, Symbols and Marks </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winterhude Hand Grotesque</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/winterhude-hand-grotesque/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:29:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/winterhude-hand-grotesque/</guid>
      <description>Characterised by rough yet highly legible hand drawn glyphs. WHG features a loose setting and a large x-height, improving legibility at small sizes. It’s a great choice to use in stamps, stickers, text banners and any other creative applications, specifically when paired with larger display fonts.&#xA;Download it free Includes: All standard Latin characters Upper, lowercase &amp;amp; numbers Punctuation, Symbols and Marks EOT, OTF, TTF, WOFF &amp;amp; WOFF2 formats One Font Weight </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europa Brush</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/europa-brush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:29:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/europa-brush/</guid>
      <description>An ultra bold brush font with a notable painterly feel. Characterised by heavy, textured brush strokes. I have done very little editing in order to maintain a dry brush style and emphasise the hand painted aesthetic. It’s application is perfect for use in displays, branding projects, logos, signage, posters, invites and more.&#xA;Download it free Includes: OTF, TTF &amp;amp; WOFF formats. One Font Weight. English Language only. Upper &amp;amp; Lowercase. Punctuation, numerals and symbols.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
