<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free and custom hand drawn fonts. on Type Services</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Free and custom hand drawn fonts. on Type Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:20:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Font Software End User Licence Agreement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:20:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/licensing/</guid>
      <description>Important: Please read the contents of this Licensing Agreement carefully before you install any Type Services Fonts or software. This agreement defines your rights as a user of the fonts and/or software.&#xA;Free Font Licence This End User License Agreement (EULA) is a legal agreement and binding contract between you (“you”, the “Licensee”) and Type Services (the “Supplier”, “Type Services” or “Harry Cresswell”).&#xA;When downloading, installing or using Type Services Font Software (hereafter the “font(s)”), the Licensee automatically agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Fonts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/custom-fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 16:39:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/custom-fonts/</guid>
      <description>Type Services accepts commissions for custom typeface designs and logo word marks. For inquiries, please get in touch to discuss your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 16:29:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Type Services This is a Typography project exploring hand drawn type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risqué</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/risque/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:30:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/risque/</guid>
      <description>Hand painted using oil pastel, each glyph is full of character and unique texture creating a natural, hand drawn feel. Perfect for display use in a wide range of creative projects and graphic applications including posters, digital painting, illustration and more.&#xA;Download it free Includes: EOT, OTF, TTF, WOFF &amp;amp; WOFF2 formats. One font weight Upper, Lowercase Western European Language Support Punctuation, Symbols and Marks </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winterhude Hand Grotesque</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/winterhude-hand-grotesque/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:29:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/winterhude-hand-grotesque/</guid>
      <description>Characterised by rough yet highly legible hand drawn glyphs. WHG features a loose setting and a large x-height, improving legibility at small sizes. It’s a great choice to use in stamps, stickers, text banners and any other creative applications, specifically when paired with larger display fonts.&#xA;Download it free Includes: All standard Latin characters Upper, lowercase &amp;amp; numbers Punctuation, Symbols and Marks EOT, OTF, TTF, WOFF &amp;amp; WOFF2 formats One Font Weight </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europa Brush</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fonts/europa-brush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:29:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fonts/europa-brush/</guid>
      <description>An ultra bold brush font with a notable painterly feel. Characterised by heavy, textured brush strokes. I have done very little editing in order to maintain a dry brush style and emphasise the hand painted aesthetic. It’s application is perfect for use in displays, branding projects, logos, signage, posters, invites and more.&#xA;Download it free Includes: OTF, TTF &amp;amp; WOFF formats. One Font Weight. English Language only. Upper &amp;amp; Lowercase. Punctuation, numerals and symbols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:17:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Don’t fill this out if you&#39;re human: What’s your name? What’s your email? Your message Submit Legal stuff Type Services or typeservices.co is a trading name of: Studio HC Ltd, Company No. 9442649, 122a Spa Road, London, SE16 3FF, United Kingdom.&#xA;Font Licencing For information about how you can use Type Services Fonts please refer to the Type Services End User Licence Agreement.&#xA;Privacy Policy For those interested in what data Type Services collects, what is done with it and how it’s keep it safe please read the Type Services Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:17:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Scope This privacy policy describes how Type Services handles your personal information and applies only to personal information collected through this website or via Gumroad, which I use to sell fonts.&#xA;Information collected Type Services does not collect your personal information unless you choose to give it to us. If you choose only browser this website no identifiable information will be collected.&#xA;There are 2 ways you can choose to share your information:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:16:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Type Services is the type design practice of Harry Cresswell. Currently the project explores texture and imperfection in hand drawn typography.&#xA;Credits This site is built using Hugo, the Go based static site generator. The site is hosted directly from a GitHub repository and served on the JAMstack by Netlify.&#xA;Type is currently set using system defaults, meaning it will render differently depending on your operating system. I’m using a fluid type mixin developed by Mike Riethmuller to make type responsive for different screen resolutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free fonts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/free-fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 15:15:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/free-fonts/</guid>
      <description>All Type Services fonts are currently available for free.&#xA;To get hold of any font for free visit the Fonts page and hit the download link. To start the download, enter ‘0’ and hit ‘I want this!’ in the form. Please read the licensing information if you’re unsure how you can use your new font.&#xA;One Tree Planted For every donation of £2 or more, £1 of your donation will go towards the OneTreePlanted.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
